Stewart L. Udall papers, 1950-2010
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Papers of Stewart L. Udall, 1950-2010
AZ 372
The collection is predominantly composed of Stewart Lee Udall's professional and public papers.
Udall, Stewart L.
102 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Stewart Lee Udall was born in St. Johns, Arizona, on January 31, 1920. He was the son of former Arizona Supreme Court Justice Levi S. Udall and Louise Lee Udall. His brother was former Congressman Morris "Mo" K. Udall. The University of Arizona Library, Special Collections, houses the papers of Stewart Udall (AZ 372) and other members of the Udall family including noted Mormon pioneer and church leader David King Udall (MS 294), Levi S. Udall (MS 293) and Morris King Udall (MS 325).
Stewart's childhood and public school years were spent in St. Johns, Arizona, a rural town which developed into a Mormon community founded by Stewart's grandfather. As a young man, Stewart left St. Johns to attend the University of Arizona. He interrupted his studies to perform other duties which included two years as a Mormon missionary in New York and Pennsylvania, and military service in the United States Air Force as a World War II gunner in Europe. In 1946, Stewart was a member of the first University of Arizona basketball team to play at the National Invitational Tournament at Madison Square Garden. Shortly after graduating from the University in 1948 with a law degree, Stewart started his own practice. About two years later, he and his brother Morris opened up a firm together in Tucson, Arizona.
In 1954, Stewart was elected to Congress from Arizona. He served on the United States House of Representatives Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs (1955-1960); the House, Education and Labor Committee (1955-1956); and the House Committee on Education and Labor (1957-1960). During the 85th Congress (1957-1958), Stewart served on a Joint Committee on Navajo-Hopi Indian Administration.
Stewart was instrumental in persuading Arizona Democrats to support Senator John F. Kennedy during the 1960 Democratic Nomination Convention. He was appointed by President Kennedy to serve as Secretary of the Interior, a position he held for nine years.
Highlights from his Cabinet career are The Wilderness Bill; The Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; the expansion of the National Park System to include four new national parks, six new national monuments, eight seashores and lakeshores, nine recreation areas, twenty historic sites, and fifty-six wildlife refuges; and the creation of The Land and Water Conservation Fund. After leaving government service in 1969, Stewart went on to teach for a year at Yale Universities School of Forestry as a Visiting Professor of Environmental Humanism.
Stewart Udall continued to contribute to the nations' affairs as an author, historian, scholar, lecturer, environmental activist, lawyer, naturalist, and citizen of the outdoors. During the energy crisis in the 1970s, Stewart advocated the use of solar energy as one remedy to the crisis. He pressed the courts and Congress to compensate uranium workers and their families for damages suffered by them while living near and working in uranium mines during the Cold War years. As a member of an environmental organization, the Natural Resources Defense Council, Stewart defended the Environmental Protection Agency against closure due to budgetary cuts. Stewart was elected to the Central Arizona Water Conservation Board and commissioned as a member of the Arizona Parks Task Force. Stewart and Lee Udall moved from Phoenix to New Mexico in 1989 where Stewart Udall maintained an active life of writing, travelling, hiking and advocating for protection of the environment. His wife Lee, to whom Stewart was married for 55 years, died in 2001. Stewart and Lee had six children (4 boys and 2 girls). Their son Tom Udall was elected to the U.S. Senate from New Mexico in 2008. In November 2009, the Morris K. Udall Foundation, located in Tucson, Arizona, officially changed its name to the Morris K. and Stewart L. Udall Foundation in an effort to recognize and honor the important contributions of both of the Udall brothers. Stewart Udall died on March 20, 2010 at the age of 90.
Organization
This collection is organized into eight series:
Series I: Campaign and Congressional Materials, 1954-1960
Series II: Dept. of the Interior, 1961-1968
Series III: Activity Files, 1970-2010
Series IV: Overview Corporation, 1968-1974
Series V: Personal Items, 1950- 1977
Series VI: Publications, 1957-1977
Series VII: Films, Tape Recordings and Photographs, 1958-1969
Series VIII: Recent Additions to the Collection, 1940-2010
Scope and Content Note
The collection is predominantly composed of Stewart Lee Udall's professional and public papers. Items of the 84th, 85th, and 86th Congresses are organized into administration and legislation files. Administration includes routine office matters, requests, and correspondence relating to particular problems or issues. Legislation encompasses correspondence arranged by subject, related bills, hearings, clippings, speeches, and background materials.
The three major subseries of the Dept. of the Interior papers are issues and achievements; speeches, events, and ceremonies; and administrative files. Substantial material is present on the issue of Colorado River water usage.
Personal items include photographs, articles about the Udall family, honors and awards, and letters from special correspondents. Among these are Carl Sandburg, Wallace Stegner, Ansel Adams, William R. Matthews, Frank E. Masland, Charles A. Lindbergh, Lewis W. Douglas, and David R. Brower.
Publication files contain newspaper and magazine articles, 1957-1977; Newsday columns, 1970-1972; and oversize items, 1961-1973. Drafts, correspondence, fan mail, and awards relate to his books The Quiet Crisis, 1963; 1976: Agenda for Tomorrow, 1968; and The Energy Balloon, 1974. Audio-visual items throughout the collection include an oral history interview of Udall from 1970, films, phonograph records of radio shows, and tape recordings of conferences and other public events. Twenty-five photographs of President Kennedy at various public functions are also present.
Access Terms
Udall, Stewart L.
Sandburg, Carl
Adams, Ansel
Stegner, Wallace Earle
Matthews, William R.; Masland, Frank; Lindbergh, Charles A.; Douglas, Lewis W.; Brower, David Ross; Conservationists -- West (U.S.); Conservation of natural resources -- Government policy -- United States.; National parks and reserves -- Government policy -- United States.; Wild and scenic rivers -- Government policy -- United States.; Wilderness areas -- Government policy -- United States.; Historic sites -- United States -- Conservation and restoration.; Power resources -- Government policy -- United States.; Reclamation of land -- Government policy -- United States.; Petroleum industry and trade -- United States.; United States -- Politics and government -- 1953-1961.; United States -- Politics and government -- 1961-1963.; United States -- Politics and government -- 1963-1969.; United States -- Politics and government -- 1969-1974.; Colorado River (Colo.-Mexico) -- Water rights.; Arizona -- Politics and government -- 1951-; Publications; Photographs; Correspondence
Container List
- Series I: Campaign and Congressional Materials, 1954-1960
  - 84th Congress, 1954-1956
    - Political Campaign: Correspondence. November 1953 - November 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Political Campaign: Supporters, Workers, Campaign Contacts. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Political Campaign: "Petition Signers." 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Political Campaign: Speeches, Itineraries, Publicity, etc. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Political Campaign: Photographs. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Political Campaign: Election Returns, Primary and General. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Political Campaign: Financial Records. 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Political Campaign: Scrapbook of Clippings. 1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous-House of Representatives. (Clippings and Correspondence, Committee on Education and Labor, Committee on Interior and Insular Affairs, House Subcommittee on Coal Research.) 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous-House of Representatives. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous-Stewart Udall's Congressional Reports-Statements and News Releases. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration: Miscellaneous: Stewart Udall's Speech: "The Need for New Maturity in American Political Life," Sunday Evening Forum, Tucson, Arizona. October 16, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Speeches-Lists, Notes, etc. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Congressional Ball Game. June 19, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings -Stewart Udall-Miscellaneous and General. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings- Education. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings- "Eisenhower Era." 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Foreign Policy. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings- Labor Unions. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Security Program. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Clippings-Water, Reclamation, and Power. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Publications-Water, Reclamation, and Power. 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous- Stewart Udall in the Congressional Record. 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Includes:
      Harold A. Patton's Bills, 83rd Congress
      House Rules and Manual, 84th Congress
      Cannon's Procedure in the House of Representatives, 1953
      The Congressional Anthology Poems Selected by Senators and Representatives. University Press of Washington D.C., 1955
      Appointment Calendar Book, 1955
      Voting Record (by Subject) 1953, 1954, 1955
      Voting Record (by Subject) since1947
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Inter-Office. August 1995-December 1956 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Arizona Problems and Arizona Agencies. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Indian Affairs. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Indian Affairs, Scholarships. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Foreign Policy. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Politics. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Office. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Personal. 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Fan Mail and Congratulations. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Invitations. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Congratulations, Outgoing. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Letters of Introduction and Recommendation. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Requests for Information. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Requests for Jobs. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Various Requests. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence- Congressional Record Mailing List. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence- "Referred to Rhodes". 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Radio and Television. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-Arizona Power Authority. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence-National Rivers and Harbors Congress. 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Miscellaneous Correspondence- "Crank Mail"(Forwarded from Senator J. Cooper's Office). 1955-1956 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture- Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture- Farmers Home Administration. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture- Forest Service. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Rural Electrification Administration. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Agriculture-Soil Conservation Service. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Labor. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Federal Communications Commission. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, General Services Administration-Federal Buildings in Holbrook, Arizona. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, General Services Administration-Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Treasury Department. 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Health, Education and Welfare-General. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Health, Education and Welfare. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Bureau of Indian Affairs, John Connelly Case. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Bureau of Land Management. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Bureau of Mines. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Bureau of Reclamation. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-Fish and Wildlife Service. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Interior-National Park Service. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Justice-Immigration and Naturalization Service. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Justice-Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Commerce-Civil Aeronautics Administration. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of Commerce-Various Bureaus and Offices. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Adminstration, U.S. Air Force-Niles Radio Corporation Case. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Adminstration, U.S. Air Force-Various. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress:: Administration, U.S. Army. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, U.S. Navy. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of State-Visas. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Department of State-Passports. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Service Academies-Appointments. 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Post Office Department. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Veterans Administration-General. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Veterans Administration-Charles Case Coates Case, 1946-1952. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Civil Service Commission. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Comptroller General of the United States-General Accounting Office. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Federal Trade Commission. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Federal Housing Administration. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Housing and Home Finance Agency. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Library of Congress. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Selective Service System. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 84th Congress: Administration, Small Business Administration. 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Udall Bills-List. 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Stewart Udall's Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 11, Folder 2-50)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Colorado River Storage Project-Includes Hearings before Subcommittee on Irrigation and Reclamation. February 28-March 5, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Glen Canyon Townsite-HR 11685. 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Upper Colorado River Project-Correspondence (Includes letter from Joseph Wood Krutch.) 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Upper Colorado River Project-HR 3383 and Floor Debate. 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Upper Colorado River Project-Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation: Colorado River, Various Bills, Reports. 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Central Arizona. Project-Clippings. 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation: Buttes Dam and San Carlos Irrigation Project-HR 5143, Correspondence. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation: Buttes Dam and San Carlos Irrigation Project-HR 5143, Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Hell's Canyon Dam-S 1333. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Whitlow Ranch Dam, Arizona. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Yuma Reclamation Project-H.R. 6940. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Public Lands-HR 2787, Aztec Land and Cattle Company. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Public Lands-HR 5538, Withdrawal for Military Use. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Natural Gas Act-Amendments to HR 6645 and HR 6106. 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Highways-HR 7072, Highway Bill. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Highways-HR 8836. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Highways-Various Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Post Office-HR 11380, HR 9228, Postal Rates. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Post Office-Postal Pay Raise, Correspondence. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Post Office-Miscellaneous Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Elections Laws-H.R. 3139, H.R. 1767 (Correspondence, Speeches). 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Elections Laws-H.R. 3139, H.R. 1767 (Clippings, Background Material). 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Federal Aid to Schools-H.R. 7535, School Construction. 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Federal Aid to Schools-H.R. 6803, H.R. 11263, School Construction and Integration. (Includes letter from Adlai Stevenson, February 23, 1956.) 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Federal Aid to Schools-Clippings and Miscellaneous Materials. 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Federal Aid to Schools-School Integration. 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Public Schools- Miscellaneous Legislation. 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Statehood for Alaska and Hawaii- H.R. 2535. 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Immigration and Refugees. 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Armed Services- Universal Military Training (Correspondence). 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Armed Services-Universal Military Training (Form Letter Replies.) 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Armed Services-Various Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Foreign Affairs- H.J.R. 309, the "Status of Forces Treaty". 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Veterans-H.R. 7886, Pension Increases. 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Veterans-H.R. 7886, Pension Increases (Petitions). 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Veterans-Various Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture (1956 Farm Bill). 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture -Various Bills that Include Price Supports, Farm Credits, Humane Slaughter, Poultry Inspection, Soil Bank, etc. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Agriculture, Miscellaneous. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Alaskan Hospital Bill-H.R. 6376. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Alcoholic Beverages-H.R. 4627, H.R. 7922, H.R. 8000. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Automobile Dealers Franchise-H.R. 11360, S. 3879 ("Good Faith Bill"). 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Banking. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Civil Service and Retirement-Various Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, H.R. 2117, S. 67-Employee Pay Raise. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, H.R. 3792-Retirement Benefits. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, S. 2875-Revise Civil Sevice Retirement Act. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Federal Construction Contract Act-S. 1644. 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Health and Medicine. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Indian Affairs-H.R. 30 (Subcommittee Hearings, Tucson, Arizona). 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Indian Affairs-H.R. 2682, Mineral Lands within the Papago Indian Reservation. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Indian Affairs-H.R. 5313, H.R. 5566-Amend Indian Claims Commission Act. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Indian Affairs-Various Bills. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Labor-Amend Railroad Retirement Act. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - 84th Congress: Legislation, Labor and Wages. 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 8)